const questions = [
    { question: "Which among the following language is oldest among the cosmos?", options: ["Java", "Kotlin", "Dart", "Swift"], correct: "Java" },

    { question: "Which of the following is front-end language?", options: ["Java", "Python", "Javascript", "C++"], correct: "Javascript" },

    { question: "Which of the following is back-end language?", options: ["HTML", "CSS", "SCSS", "Python"], correct: "Python" },

    { question: "Which of the following is Markup language?", options: ["HTML", "C++", "Javascript", "Java"], correct: "HTML" },

    { question: "Which of the following is Scripting language?", options: ["Kotlin", "Javascript", "C++", "Java"], correct: "Javascript" },

    { question: "In C a preprocessor directive is a statement that begins with_____", options: ["/", "#", "/*", "*"], correct: "#" },

    { question: "In C which character always ends a statement?", options: [";", "+", "/*", ")"], correct: ";" },

    { question: "JavaScript is a ___ -side programming language.", options: ["Client", "Server", "Both", "None"], correct: "Both" },

    { question: "How do you find the minimum of x and y using JavaScript?", options: ["min(x,y);", "Math.min(x,y)", "Math.min(xy)", "min(xy);"], correct: "Math.min(x,y)" },

    { question: "Which JavaScript label catches all the values, except for the ones specified?", options: ["catch", "label", "try", "default"], correct: "default" }
]

export default questions